

ANDREI BRATILA

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER



CONTACT

+34 643 06 99 12

andreiflorianbratila@gmail.com

Tarragona

andreiflorianbratila.dev

■ Willing to Relocate for Work

Own Vehicle

EDUCATION

2022 **DEVTALLES**

• FullStack Developer JS

2018-2020 **CAL·LÍPOLIS**

· Medical Imaging and Nuclear Medicine

SKILLS

Advanced NextJs NestJs Intermediate Intermediate Gsap Git Intermediate **Typescript** Intermediate **TailwindCss** Advanced Intermediate Phaser **Nginx** Low Framer Motion Low Prisma Advanced

IDIOMAS

 Spanish **Native** Romanian Native Catalán **Native** English Intermediate-High

PERFIL

I'm a FullStack developer with experience in TypeScript, Next.js and Nest.js, specialized in web applications and Web3 (smart contracts in Solidity and Metamask in BSC). I have knowledge in VPS administration, auto-deployment with webhooks, and configuring Nginx as a reverse proxy.

EXPERIENCIA

WowWebGroup

NOVEMBER2024 - PRESENT

FullStack Developer

- · Responsible for creating an admin panel, the database, and securing the website.
- Implementation of auto-deployment on VPS with Nginx and webhook.













WowWebGroup

unitdreams.com

OCTOBER 2024

FullStack Developer

- Developed a website based on a Figma design and created an admin panel to modify website parameters.
- · Configured PostgreSQL on server and auto-deployment on VPS.

















Private Development

JANUARY 2024 - OCTOBER 2024

FullStack & SmartContract Developer

- Created a DApp connected to Metamask on the BSC network.
- Developed smart contracts in Solidity (locking contracts, NFTs, tokens, pre-sales, token burning, etc.).
- Implementation of auto-deployment on VPS with webhooks, including automated deployment of smart contracts.

















La Pizza de Hugo <u>lapizzadehugo.com</u>

AUGUST 2023

FullStack Developer

Responsible for creating and designing the company website.







